Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2012 - Series IV: Periodical Collection, 242504
  - Graphis 296, 1995; 242541 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 12)
  - Horizon: The Magazine of the Arts (March 1980), 242542 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 13)
  - Insight (Dec. 1988), 242543 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 14)
  - Jesús Carles Villallonga - Antològica 1945-1976, 242544 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 15)
  - Kodak Professional Forum - vol. 6, no. 1 (two copies), 1983; 242545 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 16)
  - L'Officiel - Festival International Du Film D'Animation, 2008; 242546 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 17)
  - Memories - The Magazine of Then and Now (Feb./March 1990), 242547 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 18)
  - The Movie - The Illustrated History of the Cinema - Chapter 33, 1980; 242548 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 19)
  - New York University Magazine (Fall 1989) (two copies), 242549 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 20)
  - Platform International Animation Festival, 2007; 242550 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 21)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1983), 242551 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 22)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Jan./Feb. 1988), 242552 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 23)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 1989), 242553 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 24)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Sept./Oct. 1990), 242554 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 25)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1993), 242555 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 26)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Sept./Oct. 1994), 242556 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 27)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Jan./Feb. 1995), 242557 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 28)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1996), 242558 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 29)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 1998), 242559 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 30)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 2000), 242560 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 31)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (July/Aug. 2000), 242564 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 32)
  - Print Magazine (Sept./Oct. 2006), 242565 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 33)
  - Print Magazine (Oct. 2010), 242566 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 34)
  - Sightlines - vol. 12 no. 2 (Winter 1978/79), vol. 12 no. 4 (Summer 1979), 1978; 1979; 242567 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 1)
  - Sightlines - vol. 18 no. 3 (Spring 1985), vol. 18 no. 4 / vol. 19 no. 1 (Summer/Fall 1985), 242568 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 2)
  - Sightlines - vol. 19 no. 2 (Winter 1985/86) (2 copies), 1985; 1986; 242569 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 3)
  - Sightlines - vol. 19, nos. 3/4 (Spring/Summer 1986), vol. 20 no. 1 (Fall 1986), 242570 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 4)
  - Sightlines - vol. 20 no. 3 (Spring 1987), vol. 20 no. 4 / vol. 21 no. 1 (Summer/Fall 1987), 242571 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 5)
  - Sightlines - vol. 21 no. 2 (Winter 1987/88), vol. 22 no. 2 (Spring 1989), 1987; 1988; 1989; 242572 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 6)
  - Take One - The Magazine of the Movies - vol. 6 no. 12 (1978), vol. 7 no. 8 (1979), 1978; 1979; 242573 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 7)
  - Trinity News - The Magazine of Trinity Church in the City of New York - vol. 40 no. 3 (1993), 242574 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 8)
  - The Velvet Light Trap - Review of Cinema no. 24 (Fall 1989), 242575 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 9)
  - Subseries G: "Two Guys Named Joe", 243678
    - Joe Grant. Letters; Story Meeting Drafts; Miscellaneous "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1934-1941; 1994-1995; 243679 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 19)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research, 1908-1942; 2007-2008; 243680 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 20)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Publicity + Promotion, May - October 2010; 243681 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 21)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [1 of 4], undated; 243682 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 22)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [2 of 4], undated; 243683 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 23)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [3 of 4], undated; 243684 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 24)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [4 of 4], undated; 243685 (Box 2012.VI.D.F.8, Folder 25)
- Accretions 2012 - Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection, 242562
  - Side A: Dede Allen, AMPAS, New York City; Side B: Willis Pyle, New York City, November 7, 2006/November 9, 2006; ID: 040.0265; 242563 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0265, Case 040.0265)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell UR 120
  - Leonard Marcus on J.P. Miller, January 15, 2007; ID: 040.0266; 242761 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0266, Case 040.0266)
  - Charles Solomon on Joe Grant, July 22, 2007; ID: 040.0267; 242793 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0267, Case 040.0267)
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Memorex DBS 90
  - Howard E. Green, Los Angeles, July 23, 2007; ID: 040.0268; 242794 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0268, Case 040.0268)
    Duration: 51 minutes
  - Side A: Carol Grubb, Los Angeles, part I Side B: Carol Grubb, Los Angeles, part II, July 23, 2007; ID: 040.0269; 242795 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0269, Case 040.0269_pt.1, Case 040.0269_pt.2)
  - Carol Grubb, LA, part III, July 23, 2007; ID: 040.0270; 242796 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0270, Case 040.0270)
    Duration: 54 minutes
  - Jennifer Castrup, Los Angeles, July 24, 2007; ID: 040.0271; 242797 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0271, Case 040.0271)
    Duration: 76 minutes
  - Side A: Andreas Deja, Los Angeles, Side B: Don Hahn, July 25, 2007/July 27, 2007; ID: 040.0272; 242798 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0272, Case 040.0272)
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Sony HF 60
  - Side A: Eric Goldberg w. Disney Feature Anim. Studios; Side B: Eric Goldberg, Burney Mattinson w. DFA, July 25, 2007/July 25, 2007; ID: 40.0273; 242799 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 40.0273, Case 040.0273)
  - Side A: Burney Matinson, part II; Mike Gabriel, part I; Side B: Mike Gabriel and Burney Mattinson, part II, July 25, 2007; ID: 040.0274; 242800 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0274, Case 040.0274_pt.1, Case 040.0274_pt.2)
    Duration: 92 minutes
  - John Musker, July 25, 2007; ID: 040.0275; 242801 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0275, Case 040.0275)
  - Carol Grubb (phone), July 31, 2007; ID: 040.0276; 242802 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0276, Case 040.0276)
    Duration: 18 minutes
  - Side A: Darla Anderson, Pixar Studio; Side B: Darla Anderson continued; Lee Unkrich, Pixar, August 13, 2007; ID: 040.0277; 242803 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0277, Case 040.0277)
  - Ed Catmull, Pixar, August 13, 2007; ID: 040.0278; 242804 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0278, Case 040.0278)
  - Side A: Jerome Ranft, Pixar; Side B: John Tschudan (childhood friend of Joe and Jerome Ranft), August 15, 2007; ID: 040.0279; 242805 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0279, Case 040.0279)
  - Side A: Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, California, part I; Side B: Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, California, part II, August 16, 2007; ID: 040.0280; 242806 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0280, Case 040.0280)
  - Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, CA, part III, August 16, 2007; ID: 040.0281; 242807 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0281, Case 040.0281)
    Duration: 25 minutes
  - Side A: Brad Bird, Pixar; Side B: Andrew Stanton, Pixar, August 17, 2007; ID: 040.0282; 242808 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0282, Case 040.0282)
  - Side A: Pete Docter, Pixar, part I Side B: Pete Docter, Pixar, part II, August 17, 2007; ID: 040.0283; 242809 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0283, Case 040.0283)
  - Bob Peterson, Pixar, August 17, 2007; ID: 040.0284; 242810 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0284, Case 040.0284)
    Duration: 34 minutesAccess CDs available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
  - Jonas River, Pixar, August 17, 2007; ID: 040.0285; 242811 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0285, Case 040.0285)
  - Danielle Workman (phone), August 19, 21, & 22, 2007; ID: 040.0286; 242812 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0286, Case 040.0286)
    Duration: 43 minutes
  - Brenda Chapman, Pixar, (phone interview), September 12, 2007; ID: 040.0287; 242813 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0287, Case 040.0287)
    Duration: 23 minutesAccess CDs available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
  - Tom Wilhite on "Brave Little Toaster" and Joe Ranft, September 14, 2007; ID: 040.0288; 242814 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0288, Case 040.0288)
    Originial Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Sony HF 60
    Duration: 35 minutes
  - Jerry and Rebecca Rees (phone), Los Angeles, September 21, 2007; ID: 040.0289; 242815 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0289, Case 040.0289)
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Sony HF 90
  - Ruth Ranft (phone - Joe Ranft's mother), October 1, 2007; ID: 040.0290; 242816 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0290, Case 040.0290)
    Duration: 16 minutes
  - Diane Castrup, New York City, October 4, 2007; ID: 040.0291; 242817 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0291, Case 040.0291)
    Duration: 9 minutes
  - Side A: Darrell Van Sitters on Joe Ranft; Side B: Mike Giaimo (phone), November 27, 2007/November 28, 2007; ID: 040.0292; 242818 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0292, Case 040.0292)
    Duration: 44 minutes
  - Side A: Lane Smith (phone) Side B: Jorgen Klubien, January 2, 2008/January 7, 2008; ID: 040.0293; 242819 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0293, Case 040.0293)
    Duration: 36 minutes
  - John Lasseter (phone), January 15, 2008; ID: 040.0294; 242820 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0294, Case 040.0294)
    Duration: 28 minutes
  - Susan Goldberg on Joe Grant; Carol Grubb (undated); Alice Davis on Joe Grant, Los Angeles, February 6, 2008/February 7, 2008; ID: 040.0295; 242821 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0295, Case 040.0295)
  - Carol Grubb, February 7, 2008; ID: 040.0296; 242822 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0296, Case 040.0296)
    Duration: 66 minutes
  - Wendy Wick Reeves (phone) - Nat. Portrait Gal. Smithsonian, March 16, 2008; ID: 040.0297; 242823 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0297, Case 040.0297)
    Duration: 21 minutes
  - Side A: Tom Schumacher on Joe Grant, New York City; Side B: Pam Coats (phone interview), May 27, 2008/June 3, 2008; ID: 040.0298; 242824 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0298, Case 040.0298)
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell UR 90
  - Dean De Blois (phone), June 4, 2008; ID: 040.0299; 242825 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0299, Case 040.0299)
  - Andreas Deja, Eric Goldberg, Mark Henn, May 4, 2009; ID: 040.0300; 242826 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0300, Case 040.0300)
  - Willis Pyle, New York City, July 27, 2010; ID: 040.0301; 242827 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0301, Case 040.0301_pt.1, Case 040.0301_pt.2)
  - Side A: Michael Sporn, NYC, part I; Side B: Michael Sporn, NYC, part II, August 4, 2010/August 25, 2010; ID: 040.0302; 242828 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0302, Case 040.0302_pt.1, Case 040.0302_pt.2)
    Duration: 108 minutes
  - Eric Larsen's Brother (undated), ID: 040.0303; 242829 (Box 2012.V.5, Media ID: 040.0303, Case 040.0303)
    Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell XLII 100
- Accretions 2012 - Series VI: Major Projects, 242576
  - Subseries D: Chuck Jones, 242577
    - Chuck Jones, 1992; 1997; 242578 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 10)
    - Chuck Jones [1 of 2], 1997-2007; 242579 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 11)
    - Chuck Jones [2 of 2], 1997-2007; 242580 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 12)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info [1 of 2], 1992-2009; 242762 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 13)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info [2 of 2], 1992-2009; 242763 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 14)
    - The Chuck Jones Center for Creativity, 1988-2003; Bulk 1993, 2003; 242764 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 15)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary, 1997; 2008-2009; 242765 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 16)
    - Chuck Jones Photos, 1997; 242766 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 17)
    - Chuck Jones - Turner Classic Movies, 2005-2009; 242767 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 18)
    - MacDowell Medal - Chuck Jones [1 of 2], 1989, 1996-2000; Bulk 1997-1999; 242768 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 19)
    - MacDowell Medal - Chuck Jones [2 of 2], 1989, 1996-2000; Bulk 1997-1999; 242769 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 20)
    - Walt Disney Imagineering, 1996; 242770 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 21)
  - Subseries E: John and Faith Hubley, 242771
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [1 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012; 242772 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 22)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [2 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012; 242775 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 23)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [3 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012; 242776 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 24)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [4 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012; 242777 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 25)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [1 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011; 242778 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 26)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [2 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011; 242779 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 27)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [3 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011; 242780 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 28)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [4 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011; 242781 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 29)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [5 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011; 242782 (Box 2012.IV.VI.D.E.4, Folder 30)
  - Subseries F: "The Moon and the Son", 242773
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [1 of 4], 2005-2006; 242783 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 1)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [2 of 4], 2005-2006; 242784 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 2)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [3 of 4], 2005-2006; 242785 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 3)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [4 of 4], 2005-2006; 242786 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 4)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award 2005 "Best Animated Short", 2005-2010; 242787 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 5)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [1 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006; 242788 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 6)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [2 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006; 242789 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 7)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [3 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006; 242790 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 8)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [4 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006; 242791 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Information, Congratulation Letters, Emails, Etc., 2001-2009; 242792 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 10)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [1 of 3], 1999-2006; 242870 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 11)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [2 of 3], 1999-2006; 242871 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 12)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [3 of 3], 1999-2006; 242872 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 13)
  - Subseries G: "Two Guys Named Joe", 242774
    - Joe Grant Bio/Filmography, Articles/Obits - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1941; 1992-2007; 242873 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 14)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [1 of 3], 1926-1932; 242874 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 15)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [2 of 3], 1926-1932; 242875 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 16)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [3 of 3], 1926-1932; 242876 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 17)
    - Joe Grant/Dick Huemer "Music Selections by Stokowski and Walt Disney for possible future Fantasia meeting: May 14, 1940", 242877 (Box 2012.VI.F.G.6, Folder 18)
    - Joe Grant. Letters; Story Meeting Drafts; Miscellaneous "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1934-1941; 1994-1995; 242950 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 1)
    - Joe Grant Oral History - Interview by Chas Solomon, March 2000, Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences - "Two Guys Named Joe", 242951 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 2)
    - Joe Grant Personal Interviews - "Two Guys Named Joe", 1985-1990; 1997-2003; 242952 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 3)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research [1 of 2], 1908-1942; 2007-2008; 242953 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 4)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research [2 of 2], 1908-1942; 2007-2008; 242954 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 5)
    - Research for "Two Guys Named Joe" Dumbo Original Script, 1940; 2002; 242955 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 6)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Production Info [1 of 2], 2007-2010; 242977 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 7)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Production Info [2 of 2], 2007-2010; 242979 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 8)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Publicity + Promotion, May - October 2010; 242980 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 9)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" corrected by Walt Disney Archives, version 9/15/08, David Smith and Robt. Tieman, September 15, 2008; 242981 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 10)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews and Research on Joe Ranft [1 of 2], 1987-2008; 242982 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 11)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews and Research on Joe Ranft [2 of 2], 242983 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 12)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews regarding Joe Grant [1 of 2], 1995-2008; 242985 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 13)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews regarding Joe Grant [2 of 2], 1995-2008; 242986 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 14)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Joe Kennedy's Edit 8/20/08 Excerpts, August 20, 2008; 242984 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 15)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Joe Ranft and John Canemaker: Personal Correspondence, 1988-2005; 242987 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 16)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Picture Selections - Joe Grant and Joe Ranft, undated; 242988 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 17)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Research: Dick Huemer, 1942; 1945; 1968; 2006-2008; 242989 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 18)
    - "Two Guys named Joe" Research Portfolio of Art + Correspondence (copies), regarding Joe Grant from his daughter Jennifer Grant Castrup, 1935; 1940-1946; 2005; 242990 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 19)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Robt. Cornfeld's Edit 9/8/08 Excerpts, 2008; 242991 (Box 2012.VI.G.7, Folder 20)
- Accretions 2012 - Oversize: Series I - Documentary Material, 243656
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 243657
    - Irish Animation Research & Article by John Canemaker for Print Magazine Oct. 2010, 1989; 2008-2010; 243658 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 1)
    - NYU Tenure Docket, 1979-1992; 243659 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 2)
    - "Thank You from the KCAI Animation Dept", April 16, 2009; 243660 (Folder 4 Right)
  - Subseries B: People, 243661
    - Canemaker, John - Article for D23 (Disney Magazine) Spring 2012, 2009-2012; 243662 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 4)
    - Canemaker, John - in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Aug. 28 (Mon.) - Sept. 3 (Sun.) 1995. 7th Banco Nacional Int'l Film Festival, 243663 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 5)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [1 of 2], 2006-2012; 243664 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 6)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [2 of 2], 2006-2012; 243665 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 7)
- Accretions 2012 - Oversize: Series VI - Major Projects, 243666
  - Subseries D: Chuck Jones, 243667
    - Chuck Jones, 1997; 1999; 243668 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 8)
    - Chuck Jones, 1997-2007; 243669 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 9)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info, 1992-2009; 243670 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 10)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary [1 of 2], 1997; 2008-2009; 243671 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 11)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary [2 of 2], 1997; 2008-2009; 243672 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 12)
    - Chuck Jones - Turner Classic Movies, 2005-2009; 243673 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 13)
    - "Honoring Film Animation Director Chuck Jones", 1997; 243674 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries F: "The Moon and the Son", 243675
    - "Congratulations John!" TSOA Students, Faculty, & Staff, Gift to Prof. Canemaker for Winning an Oscar, March 6, 2006; 243676 (Folder 15)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award 2005 "Best Animated Short", 2005-2010; 243677 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 16)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondenc, 1999-2006; 243686 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 17)
    - "The Moon and the Son" Scene 98, undated; 243687 (Box 2012.I.AB.VI.DF.8, Folder 18)